[Music]
there is a lot more talk about bite size
insurance now as you rightly identified
there is lot more awareness and maybe
even advertisement
but actually bite size insurance
policies have been there
at a smaller scale
uh i remember back in 2006 or seven we
had launched a 50 rupee uh you know
outpatient uh policy for the rural
markets part of our social outreach
initiative program uh of course it
hadn't kind of scaled into the you know
the
uh urban markets at that point in time
and i think the point that you're making
about you know this becoming quite uh
popular now is as i said because of
maybe the advent of two or three things
one the digital distribution which makes
it easy to uh relatively easier lower
cost to sell these products
second is i would say a large number of
fintech players you know
[Music]